A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers and OK Harris Works of Art gallery records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art AAA.okharr
Archives of American Art
- Artists' Files, 1967-2014; Series 4; 34 Linear feet Boxes 4-38, 80
  This series retains the order and labeling used by the gallery. Artists' files are identified as "Current" (active) or "Past" (no longer represented by OK Harris). Current files are categorized as "Group A," "Group B," and "Photographers." Past files are categorized as "Group A," "Group B," and "Group C." According to gallery staff, artists were grouped according to how quickly they could produce enough new work for a show. Some artists are included in both subseries; within each subseries, a few artists are found in more than one group. Over time, it appears that some artists' output changed and filing errors occurred. This series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  4.1: Artists' Files - Current, 1970-2014
  4.2: Artists' Files - Past, 1967-2014
  - Artists' Files - Current, 1970-2014; 4.1
    - Artists' Files, Current - Group A (Box 4)
      - Baeder, John, 1978-2013 (Box 4, Folder 22-27)
      - Baeder, John, 1978-2013; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 5, Folder 1-15)
      - Brody-Lederman, Stephanie, 1992-2014; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
      - Castanis, Muriel, 1973-2009 (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
      - Castanis, Muriel, 1973-2009; Includes 6 electronic discs (CD) (Box 6, Folder 1-8)
      - Celender, Don, 1970-2013 (Box 6, Folder 9-23)
      - Celender, Don, 1970-2013 (Box 7, Folder 1-21)
      - Celender, Don, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
      - Celender, Don - Exhibition Ephemera, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Chard, Daniel, 1981-2008; includes 4 electronic discs (CD); 2 computer discs: 3.5" (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
      - Constantine, Greg, 1983-2013 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
      - Constantine, Greg, 1983-2012; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
      - Del Grosso, James, 1989-2012; Includes 11 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 6-9)
      - Dudley, Randy, 1986-2014; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 10-14)
      - Dufresne, Leonard, 1980-2011; Includes electronic disc (CD) (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
      - Fisher, Bill, 2002-2014; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
      - Fox, Stephen, 1989-2012 (Box 9, Folder 19-21)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1972-2014; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1972-2014; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD); oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
      - Giese, David, 1990-2010; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD). (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
      - Ginder, Robert, 1983-2014; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
      - Goings, Ralph, 1970-2011 (Box 10, Folder 12-20)
      - Goings, Ralph, 1970-2011; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD); oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 11, Folder 1-11)
      - Gozu, Masao, 1984-2013; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 11, Folder 12-17)
      - Harrison, Allen, 1985-2012; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
      - Hughes, Manuel, 1995-2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Jin Jo, Sook, 1990-2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (DVD) (Box 12, Folder 1-6)
      - Johnson, Mary Ellen, 2012; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Kacere, John, 1971-2000 (Box 12, Folder 8-18)
      - Kessler, David, 2006-2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Lee, Daniel, 1995-2012 (Box 12, Folder 20-23)
      - Lee, Daniel, 1995-2012; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Long, Keith, 1978-2013 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
      - Lynds, Clyde, 1986-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6-10)
      - Masaaki, Soto, 1983-2011; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 13, Folder 11-16)
      - Matthews, Ben, 2001-2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
      - McLean, Richard, 1970-2014 (Box 13, Folder 19-21)
      - McLean, Richard, 1970-2014; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 14, Folder 1-9)
      - Mendenhall, Jack, 1976-2011; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 10-12)
      - Miller, Arthur K., 1997-2011; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 13-16)
      - Miretsky, David, 1999-2010; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
      - Montgomery, Steven, 1996-2011; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 19-22)
      - Muller-Franken, Johannes, 1998-2009; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - Nichols, William, 1979-2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 15, Folder 3-8)
      - Penner, Rod, 1993-2010 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Perkel, Gregory, 1995-2013; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 10-13)
      - Pfannerstill, Thomas A., 1993-2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
      - Richbourg, Lance, 1978-2013; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 16-22)
      - Rohm, Robert, 1970-2013; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
      - Saari, Peter, 1985-2013 (Box 16, Folder 11-14)
      - Salt, John, 1970-2011 (Box 16, Folder 15-22)
      - Salt, John, 1970-2011 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
      - Seguin, Jean-Pierre, 2009-2014 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
      - Sparnaay, Tjalf, 1997-2012 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
      - Stefanic, Zarko, 1994-2011; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
      - Stocker, Tom, 1994-2008; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
      - Szeto, Keung, 1983-2009; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 14-22)
      - Van Patten, James, 1993-2010; Includes 12 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Van Vranken, Robert, 1990-2012; Includes 7 electronic idscs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 3-10)
      - Weis, Ron, 1992-2014 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Wood-Ginder, Cara, 1999-2011; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
      - Zago, Tino, 1981-2014; Includes 6 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 15-21)
      - Oversized Material - Group A, Marilynn Gelfman from Box 10, Folder 4, 2004 (Box 80)
      - Oversized Material - Group A, Ralph Goings from Box 11, Folder 10, 2003 (Box 80)
    - Artists' Files, Current - Group B (Box 18)
      - Anderson, Robert, 2001-2007 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
      - Averbuch, Ilan, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
      - Bacher, Thomas, 1982-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
      - Barnes, Curt, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Bechtle, Robert, 1991-2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Beltzig, Stefan, 1981-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
      - Cho, Y. J., 1985-2007 (Box 19, Folder 8-13)
      - Cone, Davis, 1988-2013 (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
      - Falsetta, Vincent, 1986-1997 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
      - Fawcett, John S., 1970-1991 (Box 19, Folder 19-22)
      - Franke, Kevin, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 23-27)
      - German, Vladimir, 1985-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      - Hanson, Duane, 1983-1996 (Box 20, Folder 4-7)
      - Hsia, Yan, 1974-1992 (Box 20, Folder 8-11)
      - Janson, Jonathan, 1985-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
      - Kagan, Larry, 2000-2012 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Kolibal, Stanislav, 1973-1995 (Box 20, Folder 15-19)
      - Koutroulis, Aris, 1977-1998 (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
      - Koutroulis, Aris, 1977-1998 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - Kuwayama, Tadaaki, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Lakeman, Oscar, circa 1984-1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Lan, Li, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Lazarevic, Milo M., 1985-1997 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
      - Levi, Josef, 1983-2002 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
      - Levine, Marilyn, 1975-2004; Includes 1 electronic disc (DVD) (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
      - Maravell, Nicholas, 1989-1996 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
      - Menchiari, Roberto, 1989-1994 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
      - Morgan, Kenneth, 1978-2006 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
      - Nakagawa, Naoto, circa 1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Nitka, Louis, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
      - Norris, Bill, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Nowlin, Oliver B., circa 1986-1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Okamoto, Rikuro, 1980-1992 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
      - Opocensky, Pavel, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4-6)
      - Pavia, Philip, 2005-2007 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
      - Quasius, Sharron, 1980-1993 (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
      - Radetsky, Jack, circa 1979-1985 (Box 22, Folder 13-15)
      - Richards, Joseph, 1989-2007 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
      - Rudich, Richard, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
      - Sorce, Anthony, 1981-2005 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Staller, Eric, 1974-1989 (Box 22, Folder 21-24)
      - Wesselmann, Tom, 1986-2004 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
      - Wilkerson, Jerry, 1977-1992 (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
    - Artists' Files, Current - Photographers (Box 23)
      - Abrahamson, Mark, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Adams, Shelby Lee, 1993-2011 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Ahlgren, Steven, 1996-2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Aller, Robert, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Aloma, Lilyan, 2003-2009; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Barker, Joan, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Bartoloni, Gary, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Balboni, Margot, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Benton-Harris, John, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Blotnik, Elihu, 2007-2010; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Borowiec, Andrew, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Bramson, Stern, 1984-circa 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Brickman, David, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Bromburg, Roy, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Brunetti, Eric, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Burkins, Nathaniel, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Ceo, Gregory P., 1999 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Chambers, Tom, 2001-2005 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Chester, Mark, 1983-2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 23, Folder 24-25)
      - Ciardi, George, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Colmer, Roy, 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Cummer, Willson, 2009-2011; Includes 2 elelctronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Davis, Alan, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Dayan, Eddie, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Del Valle, Eduardo and Mirta Gomez, 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Deschamps, Francois, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - De Vall, Sue, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Duda, Paul Lawrence, 2005-2006; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - English, Ron, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Feldman, Gerald, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Fentress, Sam, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Feresten, Timothy, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Fretz, Stephen, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Friedman, Sarah A., 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Fujimi, Michitaka, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Fuster, Sylvia G., 2004 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Geffner, Greg, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Gerbault, Arthur, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Gianettino, Larry, 1996-2000 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Goldfarb, Anders, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Gordon, Richard, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Graves, Ken and Eva Lipman, 1991-2000 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Greenburg, Paul, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Greer, A. Roy, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Gross, Steve and Susan Daley, 2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Hafford, Jessica, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Harnett, Matt, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Hassan, Shandor, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - Herrador, Mauricio, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Hower, Bob, 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Huggins, John, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Hughes, Kevin P., 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Hursley, Timothy, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Hyma, Jay, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Iceberg, Keith, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Imes, Birney, 1978-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Jones-Sylvester, Noel, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Kemezys, Algis, 1988-2012 (Box 24, Folder 10-11)
      - Kennard, John, 1987-2005 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Koch, Lewis, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Kontaxis, Yorgha, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
      - Kwilecki, Paul, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Kurata, Seiji, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Kuzmanoff, Leon, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Lawton, Joseph, 2000-2004 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Lee, Daniel, 1993-2005 (Box 24, Folder 20-24)
      - Levy, Builder, 1996-2013 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Liffin, Joan, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Lucas, John, 1993-2006 (Box 24, Folder 27-31)
      - Marshall, Karen, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Massaia, Michael, 2011; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - May, Jeanette, 2010-2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Miller, Richard, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Monroe, Peter, 1999-2005; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Morowitz, David, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Murray, Matthew, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Myma, Peter, 2005-2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Nadle, Ken, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Nakamura, Dai, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Navarra, Tova, 1985-1991 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Nogumi, Mike, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - O'Kain, Dennis, 1993-2007; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Onyshko, Wayne, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - O'Hare, Patrick, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Perrott, Mark, 1983-2012; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
      - Powell, Luke, 1987-2003; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Pratt, Greta, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Putnam, Michael, 2002-2010 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Ranard, John, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Raney, Susan, 2003-2008; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Rosenheim, Jeff L., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Rubin, Jeffrey, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 20-22)
      - Rupp, Sheron, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - St. Michael, Jonas, 2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Salvo, Dana, 1990-1999 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Scruton, Fred, 2003-2013 (Box 25, Folder 26-27)
      - Seccombe, David, 2006; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Sherer, Stan, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Shoots, Jay W., 2002 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Siegel, Steven, 2000-2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 31-32)
      - Sigman, Fred, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Sills, Vaughn, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Staller, Eric, 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
      - Stockdale, John, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Stravitz, David, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Sumida, Kazuo, 2005; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Stummer, Helen M., 1995-2008 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Suttle, William, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Teemer, Jack D., Jr., 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Thompson, Thom, circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Tilton, Miles, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Tobia, Blaise, 2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Touster, Joshua, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Tynan, Jim, 1995-2011 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Villen, Debra, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Ward, Frank, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Webber, Nancy, 1978-1996 (Box 26, Folder 17-20)
      - Welch, Christine, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Wexler, Mark F., 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Wise, Mark F., 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Wolke, Jay, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Yglesias, Tom, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Zamperdi, Luca, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Zipkin, Harvey, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Artists' Files - Past, 1967-2014; 4.2
    - Artists' Files, Past - Group A (Box 26)
      - Bollinger, Bill, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 28-33)
      - Cottingham, Robert, 1971-1979 (Box 27, Folder 1-7)
      - Woodburn, Stephen, 1971-1976 (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
      - Mikus, Eleanor, 1970-circa1977 (Box 27, Folder 8-10)
    - Artists' Files, Past - Group B (Box 27)
      - Adams, Allan, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
      - Akutsu, Shoichi, 2014; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Albrecht, Elke, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Algardi, Alessandro, 1980s (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
      - Amar, Joseph, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Anastasi, William, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Arman, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Arndt, Tom, 1973-1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Attie, Dotty, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Bakaty, Mike, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Baladi, Roland, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
      - Baur, Mike, 2008-2012 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Beardman, John, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Beck, Michael, 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Beltzig, Stefan, 2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Berger, Richard, circa 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Berhang, Mattie, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
      - Bermowitz, Alan, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Bianchi, Ben, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Bond, Douglas T., 1978-2008 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
      - Bower, Gary, 1969-2005 (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
      - Bowles, Rowell, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Bramblett, Frank, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Brandenburg, Allen, 1982-circa 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Brodsky, Eugene, 1991-2006 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Brown, Larry K., 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
      - Buehner, Fritz, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Butterfield, Deborah, 1976-1984 (Box 28, Folder 26-29)
      - Calder, Daniel, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Capps, Kenneth, 1974-1982 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
      - Chang, Kuan, 1999-2006; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Channing, Walter, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Chao, Bruce, 1978-1989 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
      - Cibula, Ellen, circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Clark, Stephen, 2004-2012; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Clarke, John Clem, 1969-1988 (Box 29, Folder 10-13)
      - Corsano, Steven, 2010-2014; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Creecy, Herbert, 1972-1978 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Cuervas, Joseph, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Daglish, Jamie, 1991-1994 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Dallas, Ben, 2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Davidson, Dan, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Davies, John, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - DeAndrea, John, 1972-2000; Oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 29, Folder 21-24)
      - Del Rosario, Mariano, 1991-2000 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Delvecchio, Darryl, 1996-2002 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Dickerson, Brian, 2011-2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - DiDonna, Porfirio, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - D'Orazio, Jon, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Douke, Daniel, 1999-2011; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Edwards, Benjamin, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Elouza, Ramon, 1979-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2-6)
      - Elsbach, Bart, 2000-2009; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Erdmann, Allan, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Erkiletlian, Romaine, 1999-2013 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Erró, 1975-1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Evans, Laura, 2009-2012; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Evans, Bruce, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Everett, Bruce, 1970s-1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Farber, Manny, 1971-1978 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Forma, Donna, 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Gallego, Christopher, 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Galles, Arie, 1972-1989 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Gardner, Frank, circa 1983-circa 1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Geyer, John Tully, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Ghitti, Franca, 2000-2011; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 30, Folder 20-22)
      - Gitlin, Michael, 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 23-24)
      - Goings, Drew, 2005-2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Gold, Sharon, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Goldstein, Jack, circa 1969-circa 1971 (Box 30, Folder 27-28)
      - Gutkin, Peter, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Hacklin, Allan, 2011; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Hammerbeck, Wanda, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harper, Robert March, 1998-2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Herbert, Tom, 1983-2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Herman, Alan, 1978-1996 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
      - Hoffman, Martin, 1973-1979 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
      - Horn, Gerald, 1978-1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Hoskins, Moses, 2006-2013; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Hrycun, George, 1980s-2010 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Jensz, David, 1993-2010 (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
      - Jimenez, Luis, 1980s-1997 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Kalloch, Sand T., 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Kazlov, Brian, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Kelsey, Steve, circa 1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Kerlin, Sherry, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Kern, Sandrine, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - King, Tony, 2012; Includes 1 USB flashdrive (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Kirkiles, Peter, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Kogge, Robert, 1996-2006; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Kosianski, Leonard, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Kraus, Pavel, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Kreznar, Richard J., 1972-1982 (Box 31, Folder 27-28)
      - Kronquist, Burleigh, 2001-2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Krugman, Irene, 1978-1982 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Lane, Stephen, 1993-2007 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Larsen, Ted, 2008-2012; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Lee, Unju, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Leigh, Harvey, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Lesson, Tom, circa 1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Levine, Marilyn, circa 1980s-2005 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Locks, Norman, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Lutzke, Richard, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Mabe, Joni, 1984-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - MacAdam, Jonathan, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - MacCormick, Neil, 2004-2008 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - MacKiewicz, John, 1991-2004 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Mangan, Patrick, 1991-2004 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Mattera, Joanne, 2006-2013; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 13-15)
      - Mayer, Edward, 1977-circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 16-17)
      - Mayertchak, Zdeno, 1990-1993 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Meyer, John, 2008-2011; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Mikus, Eleanore, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Mellon, Joan, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Meret, Sasha, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Ming, Ju, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Minichino, Gina, 2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Mito, Mary Neumuth, 1978-2005; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 25-26)
      - Moers, Denny, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Monteith, Jerry, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Moriarty, Laura, 2012-2014; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Morley, Malcom, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Moya, Miguel Angel, 2011; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Nagano, Yoko, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Nakagawa, Naoto, 1972-1982 (Box 32, Folder 33-34)
      - Nettles, Darryl, 1996-2007 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Noble, Daniel, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 36)